Guide to the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Seattle Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1918-1972; 1851-001; 8.21 cubic feet (8 boxes)
  - MAPS, SERIES XVII (Box-folder 7/39)
    - Maps, Undated (Box-folder 7/39)
  - CLIPPINGS, 1952-1968; SERIES XVIII (Box-folder 7/40-7/41)
    - Clippings Part 1, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 7/40)
    - Clippings Part 2, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 7/41)
  - EPHEMERA, 1919-1961; SERIES XIX (Box-folder 7/42-7/43)
    - Flyers, Newsletters, and Directories, 1919-1961 (Box-folder 7/42)
    - Site Plan of Building, 1955 (Box-folder 7/43)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1957-1969; 1851-004; 1 cubic foot
  Correspondence, minutes, by-laws, reports, organizational materials.
  Donated by Carpenters District Council, 8/2/1978